<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>At Your Service Help Library</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/help/</link>
    <description>Recent content on At Your Service Help Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 13:07:21 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/help/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Invalid Call Parameters</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/help/library/invalid-call-parameters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 13:07:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/help/library/invalid-call-parameters/</guid>
      <description>Invalid Call Parameters This error occurs when one or more sensor parameters are not configured. Depending on the sensor parameter, it either needs to be a string with one or more characters or a numeric value for integer and double types.
Please configure the measurement sensor parameters with a value.
Below is an example of a string sensor parameter that is not configured. In this context, simply add a value with one or more characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read-only Threshold</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/help/library/read-only-threshold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 05:21:09 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/help/library/read-only-threshold/</guid>
      <description>Read-only Threshold When a Threshold is set as &amp;ldquo;read-only&amp;rdquo;, all other nodes that template from this measurement will be unable to change the configuration values of threshold actions.
Imagine you have a group of services which must send all alerting traffic to a specific Slack channel. You would turn on &amp;ldquo;read-only&amp;rdquo; in this context. In essence, this creates a central configuration point for your alerting configuration.
If you are creating a measurement template which will be used by many teams within (or outside) of your organization, the configuration values will most likely be different per team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/help/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:30:11 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/help/about/</guid>
      <description>Help Library These documents are designed to help you use the @ys (At Your Service) mobile application.
 What is a read-only threshold?  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
