<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Libraries on At Your Service Help Library</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/help/library/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Libraries on At Your Service Help Library</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 09:45:02 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/help/library/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Is a Node Relationship?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/help/library/what-is-a-node-relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 09:45:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/help/library/what-is-a-node-relationship/</guid>
      <description>Node Relationships Node relationships are the logical groupings of parent and children nodes, and the dependent relationships between nodes.
Parent / child relationships are a typical Tree data structure.
Dependent relationships are defined by a node A depending on another node B for its operation. Imagine you are building a retail app that sells shoes. Your app may depend on a &amp;ldquo;Product&amp;rdquo; service, which gives you SKU level detail about your shoes, and a &amp;ldquo;Checkout&amp;rdquo; service which allows you to purchase a pair of shoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is a Measurement?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/help/library/what-is-a-measurement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 08:54:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/help/library/what-is-a-measurement/</guid>
      <description>Measurements A measurement is the combination of a data source and threshold configuration.
Data Source A data source can be
 a script that is executed at a configured interval (i.e. every 1 minute) a service that sends data points directly to @ys  The most common data source is a (Python) script that queries an external data source such as New Relic, Datadog, etc. Each the time the script runs, the data point derived from the external source is saved to the database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Node Alerting Configuration?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/help/library/what-is-node-alert-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 06:54:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/help/library/what-is-node-alert-config/</guid>
      <description>Node Alerting Configuration Alerting configuration works like a typical logging system where you can filter what messages are logged depending on the configured &amp;ldquo;level.&amp;rdquo; For example, in production you may configure your logging level to &amp;ldquo;Error.&amp;rdquo; Any logs emitted at a logging level lower than &amp;ldquo;Error&amp;rdquo; (Debug, Info, Warning) will not be emitted.
This form provides a way to configure this &amp;ldquo;logging level.&amp;rdquo; Actions configured to Children and Dependencies will trigger if their health level breaches the respective Warning, Error, or Critical level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is a Runbook?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/help/library/what-is-a-runbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 06:18:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/help/library/what-is-a-runbook/</guid>
      <description>Runbooks When an issue occurs with a service, it is important to know what steps can be taken to quickly resolve the issue. This is the purpose of a runbook. It is a &amp;ldquo;how-to&amp;rdquo; guide to help new, and experienced, operators to resolve common problems that a service may encounter.
For example, a runbook may contain instructions on how to restart a service, provide definitions and steps to resolve issues for a service&amp;rsquo;s error codes, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Nodes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/help/library/virtual-nodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 22:06:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/help/library/virtual-nodes/</guid>
      <description>Virtual Nodes Virtual nodes are read-only nodes which inherit all properties from a template node. They may only be created, updated, or deleted from their parent node.
Virtual modes can be considered as ephemeral, although their life span depends on the context.
The typical use case for virtual nodes is that you wish to quickly assign the same measurements to many nodes. In other words, they represent an asset or service that share the same properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invalid Call Parameters</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/help/library/invalid-call-parameters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 13:07:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/help/library/invalid-call-parameters/</guid>
      <description>Invalid Call Parameters This error occurs when one or more sensor parameters are not configured. Depending on the sensor parameter, it either needs to be a string with one or more characters or a numeric value for integer and double types.
Please configure the measurement sensor parameters with a value.
Below is an example of a string sensor parameter that is not configured. In this context, simply add a value with one or more characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read-only Threshold</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/help/library/read-only-threshold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 05:21:09 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/help/library/read-only-threshold/</guid>
      <description>Read-only Threshold When a Threshold is set as &amp;ldquo;read-only&amp;rdquo;, all other nodes that template from this measurement will be unable to change the configuration values of threshold actions.
Imagine you have a group of services which must send all alerting traffic to a specific Slack channel. You would turn on &amp;ldquo;read-only&amp;rdquo; in this context. In essence, this creates a central configuration point for your alerting configuration.
If you are creating a measurement template which will be used by many teams within (or outside) of your organization, the configuration values will most likely be different per team.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
